BERTRAM L. PODELL PAPERS (APAP270) 1945-1970
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Congressional Subject Files, 1963-1970; Undated; 2; 3.0
  - Commerce: FTC Investigation in Home Improvement Industry, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Commission: Afro-American History and Culture, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Commission: Astronauts Memorial in Cape Kennedy, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Commission: Chemicals in Peace and War, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Commission: Government Reorganization, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Commission: Temporary State Commission on Water Resources Planning, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Commission: To Establish a National Security Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Committee: Joint Committee to Investigate Crime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Communications: Candidate Television Broadcast Time, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Congressional Committee: National Priorities and Resource Allocation, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Congressional Record, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Conservation: Bill of Rights, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Conservation: Marine Resources and Development Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Conservation: Mid-Atlantic States Air Pollution Control Compact, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Conservation: Susquehanna River Basin Compact, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Consumer: Department of Consumer Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Consumer: Intergovernmental Consumer Assistance and Protection Act, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Consumer: Protect Children From Toys or Other Articles, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Control Over Gun and Weapon Sales, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Crime: Assistance with the Rehabilitation of Criminal and Youth Offenders, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Crime: Criminal Activity in the 13th Congressional District, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Crime: Establishment of 7 Regional Law Enforcement Academies, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Draft Reform: Random Selection for Induction into the Armed Services, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Drug Abuse Traffic: Transportation of Drugs, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Drugs: Federal Drug Compendium, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Drugs: Generic Name of Drug on Drug Labels, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Drugs: To Establish a Commission on Marijuana, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Economic Analysis of the Transfer of the Naval Applied Science Laboratory, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Education: Programs in Fiscal Year 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Education: Aid to Children of Civilian Employees Killed Abroad, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Education: Grants for Drug Education Programs, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Education: Institutional Grants for Science Education, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Education: Loans to Citizens Studying in Foreign Schools, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Education: Medical Education Bill of Rights of 1969 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Education: National Center on Educational Media and Materials for Handicapped, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Education: Services in Child Day Care Centers, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Education: Student Loan Program, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Election: TV Debate and Presidential Nominee Selection Act of 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Environment: Amending the Rules of the House to Provide For changes in the Committee on Environment, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Environment: Council on Environmental Quality, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Environment: Daily Determination of Environmental Pollution, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Environment: Environmental Quality Index, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Federal Assistance: Catalog, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Federal Property: Acquisition for Private Development, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Federal Reorganization: Legislative Reorganization Act of 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Federal Reorganization: Legislative Reorganization Act of 1969 (Compromise) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Food: Food Stamp Act, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Affairs: Atlantic Union Resolution, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Affairs: Hijacking of TWA Jet to Syria by Arab Guerillas, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Affairs: Immediate Cease-Fire in Biafra, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Affairs: Nigerian-Biafran Relief, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Affairs: Soviet Citizens Reunited, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Affairs: Testing of MIRVs, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Affairs: Treatment of American POWs in Vietnam, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Affairs: U.S. Aid for Iraqi Jews, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Foundation: National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities of 1965, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Government Operations: GAO Disclosure, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Health: Grants for Disease Control, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Health: Grants for Training in Family Medicine, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Health: Hospital Modernization and Improvement Act of 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Health: Labeling of Cigarette Packages, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Health: National Center for Population and Family Planning, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Health: National Kidney Disease Act of 1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Health: National Lung Institute, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Health: Study of Malnutrition, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Health Insurance: National Catastrophic Illness Insurance Program, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Housing: Building Sciences Act of 1969 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Housing: Low and Moderate Income Housing Provisions, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Housing: Supplemental Appropriations for Low and Moderate Income Housing, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Housing: Transfer Airspace for Housing, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Insurance: Federal Insurance Guaranty Corp., 1969 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Interstate Commerce: Motion Pictures and TV Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Investigation on Chemical and biological Warfare, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Judiciary: Bingo Bill, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Judiciary: Citizenship for SP/4 Aaron Tawil, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Judiciary: Newspaper Preservation Act, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Judiciary: Prohibit Investigations by Private Organizations of Congressional Employees, 1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Judiciary: Public Disclosure by Public Officials, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Labor: Employment Opportunity, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Labor: Job Corps Shutdown, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Labor: Occupational Manpower Bill, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Labor: Pension and Employee Benefit Act of 1969, Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Lottery: Decline in Lottery Ticket Sales, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Maritime: Department of Maritime Affairs, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Maritime: Independent Federal Maritime Administration, 1967; 1969 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Martin Luther King Jr., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Merchant Marine: Encourage Shipbuilding, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Merchant Marine: U.S. Cargo-Preference Laws, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - NASA: Research and Development, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: Cooperative Work-Study Program, Undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: February Correspondence, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: April Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: May Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 60-61)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: June Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 62-63)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: July Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 64-65)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: August Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: September Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: October Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory Inter-Office Memo, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: Opportunities for Research, 1969; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: Professional Papers and Patents, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: Youth Opportunity Campaign, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Opportunity: Full Opportunity Act, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Opportunity: Full Opportunity Act, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Passports: Efficient and Convenient Passport Services, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Peace: Department of Peace, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Peace: Department of Peace, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Pollution: Clean Air Act, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Pollution: Comprehensive Water Quality Improvement Act of 1969 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Public Works: Metro Areas of Redevelopment and Authorization, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Railroads: Method of Computing Interest, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Resources: Engineers to Work on Water Pollution, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Resources: National Water Pollution Disaster Fund, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Revenue: Tax Sharing Act of 1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Rules: To Reform the Teller Vote Provision of the Committee of the Whole, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Safety: Section 5 of the Department of Transportation Act, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Science: National Science Foundation, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Selective Service: Prohibit Draftees in Undeclared Wars, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Selective Service: Selective Service Boards, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Selective Service: Selective Service Reform, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Social Science: National Commission on Libraries and Information, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Social Security: Disability Prior to 1967, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Social Security: Increased Benefits and Insurance for the Disabled, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Social Security: Monthly Benefits and Cost of Living, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Social Security: National Welfare Standards, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Social Security: Revision of Welfare System, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Social Security: Widow with Minor Children, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Summary and Analysis: The Case for Retention of the Naval Applied Science Laboratory, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Summary of Presentation: The Case for Retention of the Naval Applied Science Laboratory, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Tax Reform: Limit Farming Tax Deductions, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Tax Reform: Prohibit Percentage Depletion for Mines, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Tax Reform: Tax Reform Act of 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Taxation: Deductible Moving Expenses, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Taxation: Double Personal Income Tax Exemption, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Taxation: Higher Education Funding Act of 1968, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Taxation: Withholding Earnings From Federal Employees, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Transportation, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Transportation, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Transportation: Standards for Railroad Passenger Service, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Treaty on Chemical Warfare, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Bills and Resolutions, 1963-1967; Undated; 3; 1.2
  Arranged alphabetically by legislation type and then chronologically by bill number.
  This series contains material related to legislative bills. In addition to the bills, files contain news clippings and correspondence. The material in these files are from Bertram Podell's service in the New York State Assembly.
  - Assembly Bills Introduced By Podell, with Outcomes, ca. 1966 (Flat-file 3)
  - Committee on Local Finance, Bills Introduced, Assembly or Senate, 1963 (Flat-file 4)
  - Committee on Local Finance: Legislative Program Commission on Estates, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Committee Reports, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 376, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Rate of Interest on Sale of Obligations, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 378, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to the Sale of Bonds not Exceeding Thirty-thousand Dollars, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 780, To Amend the Local Finance Law, in Relation to Rate of Interest on Sale of Obligations, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 781, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Sale of Bonds not Exceeding Thirty-thousand Dollars, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 1417, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Issuance of Bonds by School Districts, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 1421, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Bond Resolutions of a Town Subject to Referendum, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Defeated Act, Intro 3967, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Material Used in Construction of Artificial Swimming Pools, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Favorable, Intro 778, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to the Sale of Bonds Not Exceeding Thirty-thousand Dollars, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Favorable, Intro 779, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Rate of Interest on Sale of Obligations, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Favorable, Intro 4040, To Repeal General Municipal Law, Providing for the Distribution of Copies of Codes to Employees of a Municipality, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Favorable, Intro 4277, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to Improvements to Golf Courses, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Favorable, Intro 4370, To Amend Local Finance Law, in Relation to City School Districts Requiring Approval of Certain Bond Resolutions, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Instructions: Local Finance Committee, 1965; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Intro 359, To Amend the Code of Criminal Procedure in Relation to the Admissibility of Confessions, 1963-1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Intro 360, To Amend the Judiciary law, in Relation to Appointments Made by Certain Judges and Justices, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Intro 362, To Amend the Voting Age From Twenty-one to Eighteen Years, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Intro 365, To Amend the Conduct of the Annual Sessions of the Legislature, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Intro 369, Creating a Temporary State Commission to Study Legislative Procedure, and Making an Appropriation Therefor, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Intro 505, To Amend Administrative Code of New York City in Relation, to Accidental Death Benefits for Members of the Police Department, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Intro 834, To Repeal a Section of Labor Law Relating to the Exclusion of Agricultural Labor From the Benefits Under Unemployment Insurance Law, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Intro 835, To Amend Aspects of Workers Compensation Law, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Intro 1322, To Amend the Conversation Law, in Relation to Private Rights in Waters and Harmless Alterations in Streams and Lakes, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Intro 1446, Creating a Temporary State Commission to Study the Problems of Commuters Transported by Railroads in New York State, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Intro 1447, To Amend Education Law in Cities with more than One-million People, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Intro 1448, To Amend Education Law, in Relation to Public Records, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Intro 1450, To Amend Education Law in Relation to Examination Boards in Cities with more than One-million People, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Intro 1451, To Amend General Business Law, For the Sale of Articles of Merchandise in Spray Containers, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Intro 1452, To Amend Insurance law for Filing a Claim Against the Motor Vehicle Accident Indemnification Corporation, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Intro 1831, To Amend Town Law, in Relation to the Cost of Public Dump or Dumping Grounds, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Intro 1832, To Amend Town Law, in Relation to the Cost of Lighting Highways and Bridges outside of Villages, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Intro 1833, To Amend General Municipal Law, in Relation to Payment of Municipal Employees Upon Separation from Service, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Intro 2106, To Amend Education Law, Local Finance Law and Public Authorities Law, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Intro 2257, To Amend Town Law, in Relation to the Cost of Traffic Control Signals and Standards, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Intro 2258, To Amend Town Law, in Relation to the Cost of Drainage Facilities, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Intro 2372, To Amend Banking Law, in Relation to Special Duties of Directors of Credit Unions, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Intro 2373, To Amend Multiple Dwelling Law, in Relation to Doormen in Multiple Dwellings, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Intro 2374, To Amend Penal Law, in Relation to all types of Hypodermic Needles, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Intro 2375, To Amend Highway Law, in Relation to Taxes on Property for Highway Purposes, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Intro 2377, To Amend the Highway Law, in Relation to the maintenance of Sidewalks, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Intro 2377, To Amend General Business Law in Relation to Definitions, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Intro 2378, To Amend Judiciary Law, in Relation to Judges and Justices Serving on Other Various Public Committees and Organizations, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Intro 2578, To Amend Insurance Law, in Relation to Fidelity and Surety Insurance, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Intro 2662, To Amend Public Health Law, in Relation to Maternal and Infant Care, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Intro 2800, To Amend Vehicle and Traffic Law, in Relation to Tests to Determine Alcohol Content of Blood, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Intro 3351, To Amend Corporate Business Law, in Relation to Certificates of Incorporation, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Intro 3352, Proposing and Amendment to Limit the Amount of Amendments to the Constitution, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Intro 3355, To Amend Education Law, in Relation to the Number of Regents College Scholarships, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Intro 3684, To Amend Family Court Art, in Relation to Auxiliary Services to Aid Family Court Jurisdiction, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Intro 3685, Proposing Amendments, in Relation to Taxing Powers of Certain Cities, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Intro 4059, To Amend Corporate Business Law, in Relation to Certificates of Merger of Subsidiary Corporations, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Intro 4060, To Amend County and Town Law, in Relation to Certification of Claims, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Intro 4061, To Amend Mental Hygiene Law, in Relation to Changing the Name for Institutes of Mental Retardation, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Intro 4245, To Amend Public Health Law, in Relation for the Care and Treatment of Persons Over the Age of Twenty-One, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Intro 4293, To Amend Workers Compensation Law, in Relation to Liability and Property Damage Coverage, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Intro 4423, To Amend General Municipal Law in Relation to the Cost of Urban projects in Towns, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Intro 4498, To Amend Banking Law, in Relation to the Amount a Bank can Lend an Individual, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Intro 4563, To Amend Decedent Estate law, in Relation to Powers of a Fiduciary, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Intro 4819, To Amend Public Health Law, in Relation to State Aid for Aid Pollution Control, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Intro 5069, To Amend Banking Law, in Relation to Lenders of Small Loans, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Intro 5070, To Amend Membership Corporation Law, in Relation to the Power of Corporations to Invert Trust Funds, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Intro 5071, To Amend Highway Law, in Relation to Control of Advertising Devices, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Intro 5072, To Amend Election Law, in Relation to the Appointment and Tenure of Employees of Education Boards, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Intro 5323, To Amend Cooperative Corporation Law, in Relation to Stock and Non-stock Cooperative Corporations, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Original Bills-Local Finance, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Proposal: Local Government Consolidation- A Means to Greater Economy and Efficiency in New York, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Resolution 25, Moratorium on Payments due During the New York City Bus and Transit Strike, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Resolution 81, Joint Legislative Committee on Living Costs, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Resolution 82, Metropolitan Opera Association, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Resolution 99, Federal Milk Subsidy Program, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Resolution 117, Assembly Committee on Local Finance, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Resolution 152, Police and Law Enforcement Agencies within New York State, Undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Resolution 153, Separate and Distinct Water Districts within New York State, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Resolution 155, Hospital and medical Resources, 1966; Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Bill and Resolution File: Corporation Laws, Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)